2010年12月 我和朋友们决定
In December of 2010, my friends and I decided
去电影院看"生活多美好"
to go see It's a Wonderful Life on the big screen.
电影似乎就是我们现在所需要的
It seemed like something we all needed.
毕竟那几天我们确实过得很疯狂
After all, it had been a crazy couple of days.
这都是由...
It all started...
验孕引发的 几天前
with a pregnancy test. （A COUPLE DAYS EARLIER)
等结果真是煎熬啊
This is taking forever.
你确定你测试方法对吗?
Are you sure you did it right?
就是在一根棍子上尿尿 还能出什么错吗?
Is there a wrong way to pee on a stick?
嘿 我能问你个困扰我多年的问题吗?
Hey, can I ask you a question  that's plagued me for years?
女人尿尿瞄得准吗?
Can girls aim?
额 那男人瞄得准吗?
Um, can boys aim?
因为好像我每两天
'Cause it seems to me like I'm taking a mop
就要拖一次厕所
to that bathroom floor every two days.
那是因为你把搞笑日历挂在厕所啊
Okay, you're the one who put the  Far Side calendar up over the toilet.
你知道我一笑就动全身
You know I laugh with my whole body.
2分钟到了
It's been two minutes.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
- 是阳性 - 是阳性? 是阳性吗?
- It's positive.  - It's positive? It's positive?
- 是阳性的 - 是阳性的?
- It's positive.  - It's positive?
阳性的!
It's positive!
是阳性的啊!
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
什么?
What?!
我从没见过这个女人!
I've never seen that woman before in my life!
不好意思 条件反射了 恭喜!
Sorry. Force of habit. Congratulations!
敬Lily和Marshall
To Lily and Marshall.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
我是说 我们从没这么开心过
I mean, we've never been happier.
我想现在没什么能打击我了
Can't imagine anything  bringing me down right now.
你没怀孕
You're not pregnant.
额 这打击到我了
Well, that did it.
-==http://www.1000fr.net==- 謦灵风软影视论坛荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
www.1000fr.net presents
老爸老妈的浪漫史 第六季第十二集
HOW I MET YOUR MOTHER S06E12
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译: warmcherry 赤道猫260 校对: evelynjiao 时间轴:短发番茄
Capture:FRM@浅|Sync:FRS@短发番茄
孩子们 在这个36小时的故事里
Kids, this is the story of the 36 hours
我们原先都以为Lily怀孕了
we all thought Lily was pregnant,
而这件乌龙也让我们 重新审视了我们的人生
and how it caused each of  us to reexamine our own lives.
因为这事发生的时候...
Because while this was happening...
你确定你验孕方法对吗?
Are you sure you did it right?
我正和Punchy煲电话粥
...I was on the phone  with Punchy,
他是我高中的死党
my best friend from high school,
最近邀请我做他的伴郎
who had recently asked me to be his best man.
嘿 Punchy 我仔细考虑了
Hey, Punchy, I've given this some serious thought.
我想我知道该怎么
I think I know how we can crush these
摆花了
floral arrangements.
啊 有主意了 快说吧 老兄!
Ah, here it comes. Hit me up, Schmos!
牡丹和薰衣草上面再配上满天星
Peonies, lavender blossoms with a  halo of baby's breath
营造一种万物回春的气息
for an ambiance of springtime rejuvenation.
震撼到了吧?
Crushed it! ?
庆祝爱情就是需要这种搞怪的调调
That's exactly the accent of  whimsy this celebration of love needs!
那天肯定会很赞
It's gonna be a magical day.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
我真希望我是个纯爷们
I wish I was a dude.
我确实希望你是个纯爷们
I do wish you were a dude.
因为我要是个爷们
Because if I was a dude,
我就会让Ted Mosby做我的伴郎
I could have Ted Mosby as my best man.
我就不会 我来告诉你原因
No, and here's why.
Ted 伴郎的职责
Ted, the best man's job
不是去想花怎么安排
is not to crush the floral arrangements.
而是陪着新郎走到红地毯上
It's to get the groom down the aisle,
因为无论他是谁 那天他都会崩溃的
because, no matter who he is,  he will freak out.
我不觉得你有那个能力
And I just don't think you have what it takes
让士兵拿起来复枪
to get that get that soldier to  pick up his rifle
冲向山
and charge up the hill.
额 你忘了我曾做过这事吗?
Uh, are you forgetting I've done this before?
我是Marshall的伴郎啊
I was Marshall's best man.
那天后来怎么样了?
And how did that go again?
0比1
O for one.
拜托 那不是我的错
Oh, come on. That wasn't my fault.
要不要我提醒你下 我的致辞可堪称完美
And need I remind you,  I gave a beautiful toast.
Ted
Ted.
0 你愿意娶1为你的法定妻子吗?
O, do you take one to be your  lawfully wedded wife?
哦 天哪 我要崩溃了
Oh, God, I'm freaking out.
我为什么就选了Ted做我的伴郎呢?
Why did I chose Ted to be my best man?
额 是啊 被一个录了七集
Uh, yeah. It's hard to take criticism
猜硬币赢百万的人批评
from someone who just recorded seven episodes
我还真是难以接受
of Million Dollar Heads or Tails.
孩子们 猜硬币赢百万
Kids, Million Dollar Heads or Tails
是一档收视率很高的节目
was an extremely popular show
但是内容却相当无聊
with an extremely simple premise.
好了 你刚抛的是
All right, your practice flip came up
背面...
tails...
但是我们的维加斯庄家说过
but our Vegas oddsmaker tells us
下一次正反面的概率还是各为一半
that the next toss is still just 50-50.
那么 Jordan
And so, Jordan,
一百万美元...
for one million dollars...
正面... 还是背面?
...heads... or tails?
这枚硬币的年份是什么时候?
What was the year of the coin again?
为什么突然迷上了猜硬币啊?
Why this sudden obsession  with Heads or Tails?
事情是这样的
Well, it turns out
这档节目有个职位空缺
that Heads or Tails has a job opening.
反... 正面
Ta... Heads.
Marni 抛硬币
Marni, flip that coin.
哦 该死!
Ooh! Damn!
所以现在 因为这个小意外
So now, because of that incident,
这档节目正在找
Heads or Tails is looking
一位新的货币旋转专员
for a new Currency Rotation Specialist.
你是说抛硬币胸大无脑的女人?
You mean Coin Flip Bimbo?
她们才不是胸大无脑呢
They're not bimbos!
你去面试了 是不是?
You auditioned, didn't you?
你是加拿大人?
And you're Canadian?!
Robin 除了那枚硬币
Robin, aside from that coin,
现在还有一样东西在不停地跳
this is the other thing that's  flipping right now.
我的眼睛一直为你而跳啊
What is my lid for you.
你成了新任抛硬币小姐了?
You're the new Coin Flip Bimbo?
是货币旋转专员
Currency Rotation Specialist.
Robin 你最好在毁了你之前
Robin, you better check yourself
好好考虑清楚
before you Trebek yourself.
你是个新闻工作者啊!
You're a journalist!
你是怎么回事啊?
What is the matter with you?
这可是在全国观众前表演!
Well, it's a national audience!
我还会穿着亮丽的礼服出境!
I get to wear shiny dresses!
Robin 你还记得你的新年愿望吗?
Robin,have you forgotten about  your New Year's resolution?
我再也不喝酒了 （2010年1月1日）
I am never drinking again. （january 1,2010）
不是那个 前面那个
No, before that.
今晚我要把这整瓶酒都喝光 （2009年12月31日)
I am gonna finish this whole bottle tonight. （December 31,2009)
还要前面
Before that, too.
我搬来这里
I moved here
是为了在一流的有线新闻电视台工作
to work for a big-time cable news channel
像是环球新闻
like World Wide News.
明年的这个时候 我脖子上要戴着
Well, by this time next year,  I will be wearing
环球新闻的工作证
a World Wide News I.D. badge around my neck.
为了向你表明我的决心
And to show you that I'm serious,
这是我今晚的第一杯 也是最后一杯
this is my first and only drink of the night.
- 好 - 好了
- Okay.  - Okay?
哦 天哪 口感真好
Oh, damn, that's smooth.
我还以为你终于能去环球新闻面试了
I thought you finally got that  interview at World Wide News.
我的确去了 但是他们只提供给我一份无聊
Well, I did, but they only  offered me a boring,
收入低 还不会上镜的研究工作
low-paid, off-camera research job.
但这可以成为 你发展以后事业的垫脚石啊
Which could be a stepping stone  to bigger things in your career.
那猜硬币也可以是垫脚石啊
Well, so could Heads or Tails.
第一位货币旋转专员进入了
The first Currency Rotation  Specialist went on
单身汉的半决赛 紧接着
to be a semi-finalist on  The Bachelor, and then,
她参加了"最大减家" 减了近100磅
she lost, like, a hundred  pounds on The Biggest Loser,
现在她完全是个名人了
and now she's totally winning  Celebrity Rehab.
看起来Robin主意已定
It seemed like there wasno  changing Robin's mind.
但我们不知道的是 就在那一刻
But what we didn't know,in that moment,
我们的世界就要发生 翻天覆地的变化了
was that our world was about to  be turned upside down.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
什么?
What?!
孩子们当你的朋友们有好消息的时候
Now, kids, when your friends have great news,
你会为他们开心 大概就一毫秒的时间
you're happy for them...for,  like, a millisecond.
但接着你就会反省自己
And then you start thinking about yourself.
哦 我的天哪
oh,my god
他们真的要有孩子了
They're really having a baby.
我的生活又是怎么样呢?
What am I doing with my life?
从周一开始 我就是个货币旋转专...
Starting Monday,I'm a Currency Rotation Spe--
哦 我在开什么国际玩笑啊?
Oh, who am I kidding?
我是个抛硬币女傻帽 而且我还单身
I'm a Coin Flip Bimbo, and I'm still single.
好了 别想那个了 Scherbatsky
Okay, let's not go there,Scherbatsky.
那又是另一回事了
That's a whole other thing.
我得接下环球新闻的工作
I've got to take that World Wide News job.
所以 隔天晚上 我们要庆祝两件大事
And so, the next night, we had  two things to celebrate.
站在你们面前的是
Well, you are looking at the new
环球新闻新任副研究员
associate researcher at World Wide News.
哦 天哪 这消息够震撼的
Oh, my gosh. That's amazing news.
什么让你改变主意了?
What changed your mind?
Marshall和Lily
Marshall and Lily.
我只是突然意识到
I just realized that
我就要有个崇拜我的小侄女了
I am about to have a little niece  who looks up to me.
我可不想做个悲惨Robin阿姨
And I don't want to be sad Aunt Robin,
衰老的抛硬币小姐 让孩子吓得一身鸡皮疙瘩
the aging Coin Flip Bimbo who gives her the creeps.
我要做个酷Robin阿姨
I want to be cool Aunt Robin,
受人尊敬的新闻记者...
the respected journalist...
给她买啤酒喝
who gives her beer.
- 什么? - 什么?
- What?  - What? Oh.
我从没见过你们这么平和的状态
I have never seen you guys  looking so at peace.
敬Lily和Marshall
To Lily and Marshall.
谢谢你们
Well, thank you.
我是说 我们从没这么开心过
I mean, we've never been happier.
因此第二天 Robin打给
So the next day Robin called
猜硬币赢百万节目组 想礼貌地拒绝这份工作
Heads or Tails to respectfully decline.
嗨 Trebek先生 我是Robin Scherbatsky
Hi, Mr. Trebek. This is Robin Scherbatsky.
但就在那一刻...
But at that moment...
你没怀孕
You're not pregnant.
我很荣幸你们录用了我 额...
As honored as I am by the offer, um...
虚惊一场 没有怀孕
FALSE ALARM!NOT PREGANT.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
他们还没怀上孩子
They're not having a baby.
那我脑子里胡思乱想些什么呢?
What am I getting all up in my head about?
研究工作听起来就很难
That research job sounds hard.
而我长得漂亮
And I'm pretty.
我真的真的很漂亮
I'm really, really pretty.
站在你面前的是
You are looking
新任抛硬币小姐
at the new Coin Flip Bimbo.
- 你接了抛硬币的工作? - 是啊
- You took the Heads or Tails job?  - Yeah.
那环球新闻呢 你的工作证呢?
What about World Wide News, your I.D. badge?
你已经许过新年愿望了啊
You made a New Year's resolution.
我还说过我不会和清洁工上床呢
Okay, I also said I would never  make out with a garbage man.
生活总是会出其不意 打断你原先的计划
Life is what happens when  you're busy making other plans.
这个姜饼屋干嘛用的?
What's with the gingerbread house?
我们正准备去看场圣诞电影
We're seeing a Christmas movie.
这个是圣诞主题的电影小吃呀
It's a Christmas-themed movie snack.
那我们就祷告今年圣诞老人 送你个女朋友 Teddy
Let's hope Santa brings you a  girlfriend this year, Teddy.
Barney上哪去了?
Where the hell is Barney?
Barney去哪了?
Where was Barney?
让我们回顾一下
Let's back up again
正在他们焦急等待结果的时候...
You see,while this was going on...
- 阳性的  - 是阳性的吗?
- It's positive.  - It's positive?!
这两位正在谈论
...this was happening.
现在她就完全是个名人了
And now she's totally winning Celebrity Rehab.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
圣诞猜谜
A Yuletide riddle.
我第二喜欢的词是哪个? 是以BON开头的
What is my second  favorite word that begins with B-O-N?
邦乔维乐队?
Bon Jovi?
答对了
Yeah.
那我第三喜欢的词呢? 也是以BON开头的
What is my third favorite  word that begins with B-O-N?
奖金
Bonus.
我年末奖金支票
As in, my end-of-the-year bonus check.
我的天哪 Barney
My God, Barney!
我也在哥利亚银行工作
I work for GNB, too.
我就拿到一张 Coasta咖啡15元代金券
All I got was $15 gift card to Costa Coffee.
那是你应得的 兄弟
And you earned it, buddy.
看看我要给自己买什么
Check out what I'm gonna buy for myself.
Dibiase西装
The Dibiase.
看到这些细条纹了吗?
See those pinstripes?
钻石
Diamonds.
这是一个人能穿上的最顶级西装了
It is the uppest a person could ever suit.
那你有没有想过 捐一部分给慈善机构?
Uh, has it ever occurred to you  to give some of this to charity?
慈善? 你真要和我谈慈善吗?
Charity? You're seriously  talking to me about charity?
兄弟 我就是慈善大使啊
Dude, I am Mr. Charity.
我可是经常和各式各样的
I frequently sleep with sixes,
邋遢的 还有年过30的人上床
chubsters, over-thirties...
我简直就是比尔盖茨慈善帮的一员啊
I am the Bill and Melinda Gates of  the sympathy bang.
嘿 各位
Hey, guys.
重大消息
Big announcement.
让我猜一猜 你也拿到巨额奖金了
Let me guess.You got a huge bonus check, too.
没有 只是Costa咖啡的30元代金券
No, just a $30 gift card to Costa Coffee.
30?
Thirty?!
- 我怀孕了 - 什么?
- I'm pregnant.  - What?!
我从没见过这个女人
I've never seen that woman before in my life!
不好意思 条件反射了
Sorry, force of habit.
恭喜!
Congratulations!
哼 Marshall和Lily
Huh. Marshall and Lily are
做的都是有意义的事啊
doing something meaningful.
相比之下 我的奖金 也没那么让我高兴了
And it's making me less  happy about this bonus.
而且 我还是单身
And I'm still single.
至少我还有这单身优势
At least I got that going for me.
那我为什么还是觉得内心空虚呢
So why do I stl feel outside  of awesome looking in?
我的人生到底怎么了?
What am I doing with my life?
我们不曾这么开心过
We've never been happier.
我想现在没什么能打击到我了
I can't imagine bringing me down right now.
哦 Marshall 你只是觉得你快乐
Oh, Marshall, you only think you're happy.
先别急 因为今晚
Just wait, because tonight,
是Barney最爱大放送
is Barney's Favorite Things!
那是Barney期待得到的反应
That was the reaction Barney expected.
而实际上却是...
This was the one he got.
- 啥? - 我不知道那是什么
- Huh?  - I don't know what that is.
Barney最爱大放送
Barney's Favorite Things!
我要赠送你们很多东西...
I'm gonna give you all a  bunch of free stuff...
比如奥普拉
like Oprah.
兴奋点 好吗?
Just get excited, okay?
接下来的一小时颇为诡异
The next hour got pretty weird.
丝绒运动衣
Velour track suits!
- 丝绒很舒服的说 - 好柔软啊
- Velour is so comfortable.  - They're so soft.
遥控直升飞机
Remote control helicopters!
避孕套
Condoms!
还有重中之重...
And last but not least...
外面有一车队的豪华轿车
there is a fleet of limos outside
等着把我们载去
waiting to take us to...
脱衣舞吧
a strip club!
你会享受到膝上艳舞 你会享受到膝上艳舞
You get a lap dance! You get a lap dance!
你要在我膝盖上跳艳舞
You're gonna give me a lap dance!
每个人都享受到膝上艳舞
Everybody gets a lap dance!
太棒了
That was amazing!
这简直就是我心灵的钻石西装
It was like a diamond suit for my soul.
我得继续做好事 我要做更多的好事
I gotta keep going. I gotta do more.
不不 我不能再去那个脱衣舞吧
No. No! I cannot go back to that strip club.
我看到不该看的东西了
I've seen some things.
我也不要回去
I'm not going back either.
我要把我剩下的奖金 带去上帝的脱衣舞吧
I'm taking the rest of my  bonus to God's strip club.
第二天 他去了
The next day, he paid a visit
他所认识的最为慈悲的人那里
to the most charitable man he knew,
他同母异父弟弟的爸爸 Sam Gibbs
his half-brother's father,Sam Gibbs,
长岛一个教堂的牧师
a minister at a church out on Long Island.
Sam
Sam.
啊 父亲
Uh, Father.
我不是指父亲那个父亲 而是神父
I-I don't mean father father.
除非
Unless...
怎么了 Barney
What's up, Barney?
我在考虑
I'm thinking about
要把一些钱捐给慈善
giving some money to charity.
慈扇是你邮件里说的 那个脱衣舞女吗?
Is that the name of the stripper  you've been e-mailing me about?
你不能再给我发这样的邮件了  Barney
You got to take me off that list, Barney.
不是 我不是说那个慈扇
No, I don't mean that Charity.
那个慈扇做得很出色
That Charity is doing Peachy.
我下周就把慈善的艳照发到你的邮件
You'll see pics of the two of  them in next week's e-mail.
- 不错吧 - Barney
- What up!  - Barney,
我是个牧师
I'm a minister.
不能收这些
Unsubscribe.
我最近开始慷慨解囊
I-I recently started giving,
感觉不错
and it felt surprisingly good.
我想做更多
I want to do more.
好了 这回你终于说人话了
Well, now you're talking.
我们有个活动 是帮助那些有需要的人的
We have this program that helps those in need
让他们能重新自立
get back on their feet.
我们为他们提供吃住
We give them food, a place to live,
还有找工作所需要的衣服
clothes for job interviews.
好 我很乐意开张支票给你
Well, I would love to help by writing a check
金额是 个 十 百 千
for... one, zero, zero, zero...
你没有怀孕
You're not pregnant.
万
...zero...
噢 等等
Woops. Hold on a second.
等等 他们没有
Wait. They're not doing
为他们的人生做什么有意义的事情
something meaningful with their lives.
好了 这就改变了我的决定了
Well, this changes everything.
噢 不 我已经写下了4个0
Oh, no, I've already written four zeroes.
太好了 有小数点
Thank you, decimal point.
100美元
One hundred dollars.
太好了
That's great!
谢谢你 Barney
Thank you, Barney!
穿上钻石西装
Diamond suited up.
嘿 Ted 你能在电影院的时候保护我吗
Hey, Ted, can you spot me for the movie?
我不喜欢身上带太多的现金
I don't like to carry a lot of cash on me.
你不是说做好事的吗?
What happened to giving the money away?
是啊 Lily怀孕的时候我是这么说的
Yeah, that was back when Lily was pregnant.
可现在她不是啊
Now she's not.
所以呢 我买了件新西装
Ergo, a suit is born.
老兄 怎么带姜饼屋来
Dude, what's up with the gingerbread house?
你看起来真可笑
You look ridiculous!
这是看电影的时候吃的 圣诞主题的零食
It's a Christmas-themed movie snack!
我知道你的意图
Ah, I know that move.
你在屋子的地板下挖了个洞
You cut a hole in the floor,
她爬进去起居室 看到圣诞树 唱到
she reaches into the living room,  finds the tree...
啊 神圣的夜晚
O holy night.
不错嘛
Nice.
Marshall和Lily去哪了?
Where the hell are Marshall and Lily?
让我们最后一次回顾一下
Let's back up one last time.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
- 什么 - 什么
- What?!  - What?!
我这辈子没有认识过这个女人
I've never seen that woman before in my life!
对不起 条件反射
Sorry, force of habit.
恭喜
Congratulations!
真是太好了
This is great.
我真开心
I'm happy.
我太开心了 我的心一直在狂跳
I'm so happy,my heart's pounding.
我在狂流汗
And I'm sweating.
我简直难以呼吸
And I can't breathe.
这就是幸福的感觉吧 是吗
This is what happiness feels like, right?
啊 糟了
Oh, crap.
Lily怀孕了 而我吓坏了
Lily's having a baby and I'm  having a panic attack.
我希望他没有看出我在想什么
I hope she can't tell what  I'm thinking right now.
我可以
I can.
我也很紧张
And I'm freaking out, too!
我肚子里有个外来生物在生长
There's an alien growing in my stomach
我的子宫会爆裂的
that's gonna explode out of my vagina!
你觉得他们知道我们吓坏了吗?
Do you think the others can tell we're freaking out?
我这辈子做过什么了
What am I doing with my life?
我要拿我人生怎么办呢
我得准备明晚 看电影吃的圣诞主题零食
I should get a Christmas-themed  movie snack for tomorrow night.
他们向我们压来了
They're totally onto us.
我们要怎么办
What do we do?
继续笑就好 或许挥挥手
Just keep smiling, maybe wave.
不 不要挥手
No, don't wave!
这样说不通
That makes no sense!
我已经挥了
I'm committed.
我一直挥到我筋疲力尽而死
I'm riding this wave straight to hell.
我们走吧 那你的挥手就说得通了
Let's leave, then the waving will make sense.
随后Marshall和Lily回家了
So Marshall and Lily headed home.
Lily我们得放松
Lily, we have to relax.
没有必要那么紧张
There's no need to panic.
是啊 很多事情要去做
True, there's a lot to do,
但是我们有九个月的时间去准备
but we've got nine months to prepare.
所以我建议我们列一个清单
So I say that we just  make a list of everything
上面写着孩子出生之前 我们要做的事情
that needs to get done  before the baby arrives
今晚就把清单上面的事情都做好
and do everything on that list tonight!
我们就去做
Let's do it!
好 就去做 (读每一本关于婴儿的书)
Uh-huh, got it. (READ EVERY BABY BOOK)
好 看起来挺简单的
Okay, that seems easy.
粉刷幼儿房 (粉刷幼儿房)
Nursery's painted! (PAINT THE NURSERY)
蓝色 万一是女孩子呢
Blue? What if it's a girl?
该死的
Damn it!
学会针织
LEARN TO LNIT
在屋里做好保护措施
BABY-PROOF THE APARTMENT
为肚子里面的孩子播放古典音乐
PALY CLASSICAL MUSIC TO UNBORN CHILD
天哪 八点钟了
Oh, God, it's 8:00!
我们要去酒吧和大伙一起庆祝
We're supposed to meet the  gang at the bar to celebrate.
天哪 好吧 听着
Oh, God. Okay, listen.
当我们见到他们 我们一定要镇定
When we meet them,  we have to keep it together.
你可以做到吗
Can you keep it together?!
不 我做不到
No, I can't keep it together!
我们见过你们神情如此安宁
I have never seen you  guys looking so at peace.
为Lily和Marshall干杯
To Lily and Marshall.
Lily和Marshall
Lily and Marshall.
谢谢你们
Well, thank you.
我们从来没有如此开心过
I mean, we've never been happier.
这真是个噩梦
This is a nightmare!
我们都弄糟了
We've done everything wrong!
ipod在随机播放
The iPod was on shuffle!
怪兽乐队的歌在播放
The Jerky Boys!
我们的孩子听到了怪兽乐队的歌
Our baby heard the Jerky Boys!
你知道吗 怪兽乐队的歌很滑稽
You know what, the Jerky Boys are funny.
怪兽乐队一点也不滑稽 他们的歌简直是噩梦
The Jerky Boys aren't funny, they are awful.
你知道吗 好了 要是你不觉得
You know what, fine, if you don't think
怪兽乐队很滑稽的话 那么我不确定
the Jerky Boys are funny, then I'm not sure
能不能和你一起共同养大一个孩子
that I can raise a child with you,  Liver Lips.
Marshall 我不喜欢这样子
Marshall, I don't like this.
我知道的 好吗
I know. Okay?
我也不喜欢这样子
I don't like it either.
就好像有一个很热的焚烧着的
It's like I have a hot, burning
压力球在我胸口
ball of stress in my chest,
没有东西可以让它滚开
and nothing will make it go away!
你没有怀孕
You're not pregnant.
哇 终于滚开了
Well, that did it.
我知道这也许挺让人失望的
I know this probably comes as  quite a disappointment.
是啊
Yeah.
很大的失望
Huge bummer.
非常让人失望
So disappointing.
你们没事吧?
Are you guys okay?
没事 为什么会有事呢?
Yeah. Why wouldn't we be?
噢 怀孕的事情
Oh, the baby thing.
管他呢
Oh, yeah, whatever.
啊 圣诞节主题零食 不错
Oh, Christmas-themed movie snack. Nice.
不要爬进起居室
Don't reach into the living room!
哇 我还以为你们会崩溃呢
Wow, I-I thought you  guys would be devastated.
你知道吗 其实我们松了一口气
You know, we're actually kind of relieved.
我们都抓狂了一天半了
We were freaking out for  about a day and a half there.
是啊 这整件事让我觉得
Yeah, this whole thing got us thinking:
或许我们对孩子的事情还没有准备好
maybe we're not ready for kids yet after all.
是啊 我们想或许我们可以先养只狗
Yeah, we were thinking maybe  we would just get a dog.
养只狗
Get a puppy!
你可以想象
Can you imagine...
这会是最美好的事情
That would be the cutest thing!
不
No!
我们看电影吃的零食
Our movie snack.
开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding me?!
你们之前一天到晚都想要有孩子
All you ever talk about is having kids!
现在你们有一点点的抓狂
And now you have one little freak-out
就想要用一只小狗来取代
and you want to get a dog instead?!
不 不能接受
No. Unacceptable!
你要回去
You're gonna turn around,
你们要回家 赤裸裸地
you're gonna go home, get naked,
像夫妻那样睡在一起
lie together as man and wife
直到Lily有孩子为止
until Lily is great with child.
现在马上
Right now!
我是认真的
I'm serious!
去去去
Go, go, go!
Marshall和Lily挨骂了
Marshall and Lily got in trouble.
还有你
And you!
Barney你穿这件西装 看起来非常可笑
Barney, you look real stupid in that suit.
你要退了这件衣服 把钱拿回来
You're gonna go get your money back
拿去给慈善
and give it to charity.
我说的慈善 不是你在邮件里说的那个
And I don't mean that  stripper you keep e-mailing us about,
尽管我们拼命哀求 你别再发这种邮件过来
even though we beg you  to take us off that list.
我不能把这件西装退了
I can't give this suit back.
Ted 我在黑暗中发亮
Ted, I glow in the dark.
我在黑暗中发光发亮
I finally glow in the dark!
纽约的罪犯们 注意了
Criminals of New York! Attention!
这个男人身上这件西装 都被钻石铺盖了
This man is wearing a diamond-covered suit!
他的裤子可以供你退休了
You could retire on the pants alone!
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas!
如果我拿来一大包的爆米花  你想要去滑冰还是...
So, if I get a large popcorn,  you want to go split-skees or...
还有你
And you...
你搬来这个
You did not move
地球上最美好的城市 不是为了抛硬币的
to the greatest city on Earth  to become a coin-flipping bimbo.
所以你必须这样做
So here's how it's gonna work:
正面朝上的话 你就要接受 在环球新闻的那份工作;
Heads, you take the job at World Wide News;
反面朝上的话 你也得接受那份工作
tails, you take the job at World Wide News.
看 你得接受那份工作了
Hey, looks like somebody got a new gig!
好吧 我明天就给他们电话
Fine, I'll call them tomorrow.
我马上就给他们电话
I'll call them right now.
喂
Hello.
Ted 我不能结婚
Ted, I can't get married!
你当然能 你爱她
Yes, you can! You love her!
你是对的 我的确爱她 谢谢你 Ted
You're right, I do! Thanks, Ted!
要一张"生活多美好"的票
One for It's a Wonderful Life, please.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们真傻
We're idiots.
连孩子都没有
This kid doesn't stand a chance.
- 我们已经准备好了 - 我们已经准备好了
- We're ready for this.  - We're ready for this.
这里有好多0
That's a lot of zeroes.
你肯定你没有写少了少数点?
Y-You sure you're not missing a  decimal point?
没有
Nope.
参观完毕
And that's the tour.
中午有员工会议 在那里你会见到所有人
Uh, staff meeting's at noon,  you'll meet everyone there,
但首先你要去保安室
but first you need to head down to security.
你需要照相
You need to get your picture taken.
证件用的
For your I.D. badge.
你肯定?
You sure?
肯定
Positive.
还有更多
And there's more.
你还在送给别人西装
Do you still do that thing where you give
让他们面试的时候穿吗?
people in need clothes for job interviews?
是啊 怎么了
Yeah. Why?
带它们进来
Bring 'em in, boys!
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
- 谢谢你 儿子 - 儿子
- Thank you, son.  - Son?!
这是我作为神父对你的称呼而已 我不是你爸爸
It's just an expression.  I'm still not your dad.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你要知道 你所做的可真伟大
You know, that was really cool what you did.
当我们需要的时候
When we all needed it,
你把我们领到正轨上
you got us back on the right path.
这是我该做的
It's what I do.
嘿 Ted 如果我结婚的话
Hey, Ted, if I, um, if I ever get married
而你又不是我的新郎的话
and you're not the guy I'm marrying...
那就是你的错了 继续说
Big mistake, but go on.
我可能很需要像你这么一个人
...I could really use someone like you.
你要知道 以防我因为过于紧张
You know, in case I freak out.
而抓狂
When I freak out.
你有兴趣吗?
You interested?
你是在向我提出 我心里所想的那个请求吗?
Are you asking what I think you're asking?
Ted 你可以做我的伴郎吗?
Ted, will you be my best man?
Scherbatsky
Scherbatsky...
我将会不负你所望
I'm gonna crush it.
嗨
Hi, there.
我们今晚真愉快
We've had a lot of fun tonight,
但是注意一下 这是一年之中
but on a more serious note,  this is the time of year
我们要铭记给予的重要的时刻
when we remember the importance of giving.
再好的礼物也比不上丰臀了
And there's no greater gift  than the gift of booty.
那么 在这个节日
So, this holiday season,
为什么不和有需要的人上床呢?
why not bang someone in need?
我是Barney Stinson 这是一方有难
I'm Barney Stinson, and that's...
八方支援
one to grow on.
不要
Um, no.
嗨
Hi, there.
要知道 我们今晚真愉快
You know, we've had a lot of fun tonight...